ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Extension Attic (Box 12)
  - Asking Questions - A Practical Guide to Questionnaire Design, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Fundamentals of Business Law, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The High-Tech Potential - Economic Development in Rural America, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Educational Evaluation - Alternative Approaches and Practical Guidelines, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Competitive Manufacturing - New Strategies for Regional Development, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Small Business Management, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Policy vs. Paperclips, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Managing for Profit: Successful Sawmill Management, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Smithers (Box 13)
  - Smithers, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - PR-26, 1963-1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Most material in folder concerns the Smithers Foundation
  - Unsorted Alcohol and Drug Abuse Materials I, 1980-1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Unsorted Drug and Alcohol Abuse Materials II, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Medical Research Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor/Management Newsletters, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Operation Redblock, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Employee Assistance Programs, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Training Materials for Employee Assistance Programs I, 1966-1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Training Materials for Employee Assistance Programs II, 1974-1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Treatment of Alcohol and Drug Abuse in Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1977-1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New York City Evaluations, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Unsorted Evaluations of EAPs, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - October 11 - Field Notes, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Interviews with New York City EAP participants, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - EAERP (Employee Assistance Education and Research Program) File (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - OCA Interviews - Ed, Phil, Eileen, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    October 31, 1986
  - July Notes on EATP (Employee Assistance Training Program) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - EATP - Syracuse Field Notes - 6 week Recap, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Student File - Preliminary Interviews (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - EAP Article - Trice and Beyer, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Organization Socialization, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Handwritten Field notes, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    August 1985-February 1986
  - Smithers Awards, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Smithers Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Smithers Airline Interviews (Box 14)
  - Operation Redblock and EAPs in the Railroad Industry (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Report (Draft), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Tape Inventories (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Flight Attendants Conference, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    November 1991; includes 24 color photographs, six copies of a different color photograph, and their negatives
  - Airline Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Association of Flight Attendants-Employee Assistance Program (AFA-EAP) - Representative's Info Sheet (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Maureen Anderson, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - John Bonacorsi, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Walter Calloway, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Feuer, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - John Flasco, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Joanne Franchi, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Joanne Franchi continued, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Lyn Hackelman, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Tracy Handy, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Sandy Haynes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Pam Hollenbeck, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Allan Holmes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Linda Kuntz, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Ed (TFA), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Megan McKeough, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Midway TFA, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Marcia Miller, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mary Nearly, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Kirk Anne Neil, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Roger Patterson, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Susie Purnell, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Christine Santana, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Jean Sweet, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Ron Telles, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Kathy Tyree, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Jill (TFA), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- 21 Joint Lab/ Mng ILR 284 (Box 15)
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - Science, the Scientist, and Philosophy (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Book chapter
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - Atoms and Molecules, The Building Blocks of Nature (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - The Metric System (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - Growth and Control (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - Radioactivity and Nuclear Energy and Society (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Book chapter; includes clippings from the Stanford Magazine
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - Ecology - A Study of Interrelationships, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Book chapter; includes a clipping from the New York Times Magazine
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - The City Environment (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - Evolution and Classification of Living Things (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Science, Technology, and Labor - The Biology of Space and Beyond, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA) Course Materials, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Kenneth Gagala Correspondence, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Human Behavior and Work (Scrapbook) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Class Exercise - Westwood Regional School District example, 1970-1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Collective Bargaining Law and History in the Public Sector, 1969-1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Collective Bargaining II, 1956-1978 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Railway Labor Act and Emergency Boards, 1958-1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - The Railway Industry, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Effective Communication Course, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Carliner Materials (Textbook on Labor Relations), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Includes a news clipping
  - Mr. Louis Carliner (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Extension Attic (Box 16)
  - Course Input Academic Year 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Includes individuals' Social Security Number
  - Course Input Summer 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Saul Wallen Account Academic Year 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Includes bank account numbers
  - Instructor Payroll Fall 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Payroll Forms Fall 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Instructor Payroll Winter 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Payroll Forms Winter 1985 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Instructor Payroll Spring 1985, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Includes individuals' Social Security Number; includes a late payment from 1987
  - Payroll Forms Spring 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Forms and Part Time Help, 1978-1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - ILR School's Statewide Labor Studies Program Material, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Instructors Meeting December 4, 1976 New York City, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - The Age of Employment - A Secondary School Curriculum in Labor Relations 1975, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Daily Follow-Up Material, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - File (Labor Studies), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Advanced Seminar in OSHA - Summer School 1981 (folder 1), 1972-1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Advanced Seminar in OHSA (folder 2), 1970-1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - ADABAS (Adaptable Data Base System), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - NATURAL User's Guide (folder 1), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - NATURAL (folder 2), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Continuation of the user's guide in folder 19 of this box
  - Report on the Student Records and Registration Processes, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Smithers (Box 17)
  - Smithers General Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Smithers Symposia, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Smithers Awards May 1988, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Smithers 1987-1988, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Smithers Grants and Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Smithers 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Smithers Grant Proposals 1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Smithers Grant Proposals 1986 continued (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Smithers 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Smithers 1988, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Smithers Proposals to be read by April 1, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Smithers Proposals Fall 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Smithers 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Inactive Grants & Proposals (Box 18)
  - Cost Effectiveness Analysis of OSHA Regulations on Asbestos, Lead, and Silica - National Science Foundation - Jacob Kaufman, 1980- 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Includes individual's Social Security Number
  - Cost Effectiveness Analysis of Two Techniques for Job Search - Jacob Kaufman, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Creating Jobs and Improving Work Life in New York City - Betty Lall, 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Developing a Cost Effective Network of Educational Resource Centers to Improve the Delivery of Services to the Severely and Developmentally Disabled - Ron House, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Developing and Establishing an Employment Resource Network - Ron House, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Development of a Self-Study Course on Local Government Financial Planning - Duane Wilcox, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Dissemination of the Management Simulation for Improvement of Independent Living Centers - Ron House, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - William H. Donner Foundation, Inc. - Women in Management - Jennie Farley, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Education for Equal Opportunity - Carnegie Corporation - Anne Nelson, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Education for Equal Opportunity: Advancing Hispanic Women - Marylee Bomboy, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Employment and Related Issues of Older Workers - United States Department of Labor - Jacob Kaufman, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Equal Opportunity Training for Shop Stewards - B. Wertheimer, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Establishment of Private Industry Councils - William Holcomb, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Evaluation of Cancer Prevention Training in Occupational Settings - Jacob Kaufman, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation Research on Area Labor-Management Committees - William Whyte, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Expanded Training for Retired Unionists in New York City to Reenter the World of Work - Cynthia Hosay, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - First Line Supervisory Training - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Donald Kane, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Health Education at the Worksite - NYS-OWLC and Council 82 - Cynthia Hosay, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Health Education Classes at the Worksite - Joint Labor-Management Committee - Cynthia Hosay, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - The Human Services Administration Program for Public Employees - Ron House, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Impact and Evaluation of Dislocated Workers - Buffalo and Erie Counties - Jacob Kaufman, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Study of Labor Studies Degree Programs in Colleges and Universities - Lois Gray, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Independent Living Management Program - Ron House, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Industrial Relations TV Series - Robert Pasciullo, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Innovations in Employee-Management Relationships - Robert Pasciullo, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Intergovernmental Network for Technical Training and Assistance - Robert Pasciullo, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Labor Education Programs and the Participation of Women, Blacks, and Hispanics - Lois Gray, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Labor Relations Certificate Program - Long Distance Learning Program - Robert Pasciullo, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Labor Relations Training for Lower and Middle Level Supervisory Personnel - Jacquelyn Miller, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Management Development - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation - Donald Kane, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - A Management Training Simulation for Community Residences for the Developmentally Disabled - HDS/Division of Grants and Contract Management - Ron House, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Research and Training Center in Improving Sheltered, Transitional, and Protected Employment and Alternative Employment Solutions - National Institute of Handicapped Research - Ron House, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - New York State Environmental Conservation Management/Supervisory Training - Donald Kane, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Training and Educational Act - United States Department of Labor - Frank Goldsmith, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Supplemental - Frank Goldsmith, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Training Supplemental - Frank Goldsmith continued, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - OSHA for the Not-For-Profit Sector - Ron House, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Overcoming Barriers to the Advancement of Hispanic Women in Community-Based Organizations - Eddie Gonzalez, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Participation of women in Labor Education Programs - Lois Gray, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Pilot Project to Reach Union Men on Working Women's Issues - B. Wertheimer, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Risk Management Training for City, County, Town, and Village Officials - Duane Wilcox, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Role of Education in Sheltered Workshops - Robert Gregory, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - School of the Sky - B. Wertheimer, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Seminar for State Officers - Shelly Chairman, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Study of Labor Union Progress to Overcome Barriers to Employment and Occupational Mobility of Puerto Ricans in New York City - Lois Gray, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Supervisory Seminar for New York State Department of Correctional Services - Ronald Donovan, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Chronos 1976-1982 - 6B4B (Box 19)
  - January 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - February 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - March 1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - April 1982 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - May 1982 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - June 1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - July 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - August 1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - September 1982 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - October 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - November 1982 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - December 1982 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - January 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - February 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - March 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - April 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - May 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - June 1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - July 1981 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - August 1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - September 1981 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - October 1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - November 1981 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - December 1981 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - January 1980 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - February 1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - March 1980 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - April 1980 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - May 1980 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - June 1980 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - July 1980 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - August 1980 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - September 1980 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - October 1980 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - November 1980 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - December 1980 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - January 1979 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - February 1979 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - March 1979 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - April 1979 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - May 1979 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - June 1979 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - July 1979 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - August 1979 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - September 1979 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - October 1979 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - November 1979 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - December 1979 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - January 1978 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - February 1978 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - March 1978 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - April 1978 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - May 1978 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - June 1978 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - July 1978 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - August 1978 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - September 1978 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - October 1978 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - November 1978 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - December 1978 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - January 1977 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - February 1977 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - March 1977 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - April 1977 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - May 1977 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - June 1977 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - July 1977 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - August 1977 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - September 1977 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - October 1977 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - November 1977 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - December 1977 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Chrono File - 1976 August (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Chrono File - 1976 October (Box 19, Folder 74)